http://www.abcouncil.ab.ca/privacy/

Privacy Policy - Alberta Insurance Council
Login
Search for:
Look up an Agent/Agency
Questions?
Apply
Questions?
Exam
Schedules & Locations
About Exams
Exam Fees
Register (Login)
Examination Fees
Register (Login)
My results
Exam FAQs
Education Providers
General Insurance Exam Preparation
General Level 1 Qualification Program (GLQP)
Council Decisions
Questions?
Enforcement & Decisions
Council Decisions and Decisions of the Insurance Councils Appeal Board
Notices to the Profession (coming soon)
Guide for Self-Represented Litigants (coming soon)
Look up an Agent/Agency
Questions?
Apply
Questions?
Exam
Schedules & Locations
About Exams
Exam Fees
Register (Login)
Examination Fees
Register (Login)
My results
Exam FAQs
Education Providers
General Insurance Exam Preparation
General Level 1 Qualification Program (GLQP)
Council Decisions
Questions?
Enforcement & Decisions
Council Decisions and Decisions of the Insurance Councils Appeal Board
Notices to the Profession (coming soon)
Guide for Self-Represented Litigants (coming soon)
Look up an Agent/Agency
Questions?
Apply
Questions?
Exam
Schedules & Locations
About Exams
Exam Fees
Register (Login)
Examination Fees
Register (Login)
My results
Exam FAQs
Education Providers
General Insurance Exam Preparation
General Level 1 Qualification Program (GLQP)
Council Decisions
Questions?
Enforcement & Decisions
Council Decisions and Decisions of the Insurance Councils Appeal Board
Notices to the Profession (coming soon)
Guide for Self-Represented Litigants (coming soon)
Privacy Policy
The Alberta Insurance Council, the Insurance Adjusters’ Council, the General Insurance Council and the Life Insurance Council (the “Councils”) are “public bodies” pursuant to the Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act, R.S.A. 2000, Chapter F-25 (the “FOIP Act“).  The FOIP Act aims to balance the right to access records in the possession or control of a public body with the right of an individual to protect his/her personal information which has been collected and/or is held by a public body.
You can make a request for access to your own personal information, which may include a request to correct any personal information in the possession or control of the Councils.  You can also make a request for general information.  There are different fees associated with the different types of requests.
Prior to making a formal request for access to information, please review this web site in order to determine whether the record you are looking for has been published.  If it has not been published, you may contact the FOIP Coordinator in order to discuss whether access to the information can be granted or whether there may be another source for the information which you are seeking.  If an informal request for access to information is denied, you can make a formal request by completing the Request to Access Information Form or submitting a detailed request in writing, along with the required fee, to the FOIP Coordinator.
The FOIP Coordinator for the Councils is:
Director of Legal and Regulatory Affairs
Suite 500, 222 – 58 Avenue SW
Calgary, Alberta, CANADA
T2H 2S3
1-403-233-2929 (phone)
1-403-233-2990 (fax)
Ultimately, you have the right to request a review of a decision made by a public body by the office of the Information and Privacy Commissioner.  You may obtain more information in relation to the role of the Office of the Information and Privacy Commissioner from their website:  www.oipc.ab.ca.
Home
Privacy
Terms of Use & Refund Policy
© 2015 Alberta Insurance Council
Website Design & Developed by Codesign
© 2015 Alberta Insurance Council
